<resources>
    <string name="app_name">COling</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="terms1" translatable="false">
        <![CDATA[
    <em><big>Hello!</big></em><br/><br/><p>Thank you for using the COling service. We would appreciate it if you could read the terms and conditions below by COling, which provides a 100-day challenge to solve Corona Blue.</p><br/><br/><h3>Account Related</h3><br/><p>COling can only create an account via e-mail for thorough personal information protection of inventory management. You can access with your existing ID and password to continue using the service on other mobile devices. <br/><br/><b>You may not approve account creation in the following cases. </b><br/><br/> - Where you intends to create an account using personal information, such as another person&apos;s name or mobile phone number. - You do not enter the information required to create an account, or you have entered false information. - Where COling has deleted or disciplined the relevant account for justifiable reasons, such as violation of operating principles or laws in the past - Where identified by a mobile phone number with a history of transaction fraud, such as a fraudulent information collection website or a government agency website</p>   <br/>   <br/>   <p>   <h3>What to be cautious about when using</h3><br/>If the COling user uses the service in the wrong way or in the wrong way as shown below <b>You may impose restrictions on the use (discontinuation, forced withdrawal, etc.).<br/><br/> - Accessing the COling service by means other than the way it is guided or interfering with the provision of the service in the wrong way  <br/> - Unauthorized collection, use, or provision of information from other users   <br/> - Use of services for profit or publicity purposes   <br/> - copying, modifying, distributing, selling, transferring, lending, providing collateral or allowing other persons to use the COling service or any part of the software contained therein without the consent of  COling  <br/> - Replicating, disassembling, imitating, or otherwise modifying the COling service, such as the reverse design of software or attempting to extract the source code;  <br/> - Failure to comply with all terms and conditions or policies of the relevant statutes, inventory warehouses   </p>   <br/><br/><br/>   <h3>Privacy Related</h3>   <p><br/>Personal information is used only for the purposes and scope agreed by the user for the smooth provision of inventory warehouse services. Please refer to the inventory warehouse personal information processing policy for other details regarding personal information protection of personal information.

        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="terms2" translatable="false">
        <![CDATA[
        <br/><h3>Service interruption</h3><br/><p>The COling service may be temporarily suspended due to routine or temporary checks or other significant reasons for maintenance and repair of the equipment, which will be notified to the users via email. If the COling service is discontinued due to unpredictable reasons, COling will notify you as soon as it finds out the situation.</p><br/><br/><h3>Termination of the service contract (withdrawal of service)</h3><br/><p>If the user no longer wants to use the COling service, You can apply for the termination of the COling service contract using the menu provided in the COling service at any time, and the COling service will be processed quickly as prescribed by the law.
        When the contract is terminated, all data, such as user information or user-written posts, will be deleted except for holding user information in accordance with laws and personal information processing policies.</p><br/><br/><h3>Amend stipulation</h3><br/><p>COling may amend these terms and conditions or their corresponding notices and notices for the purpose of reflecting changes in the law or the COling service. If these terms and conditions are changed, the inventory warehouse will register the changes in the notice, and the changed terms and conditions will take effect 7 days after the date of posting. These terms and conditions apply to the relationship between COling and the user and do not generate any third-party revenue rights.</p>If the user fails to comply with these terms and conditions, COling shall not waive any rights COling has without immediate action, nor shall it affect any other provisions even if some of these terms and conditions become impossible to enforce. The laws of the Republic of Korea apply to these Terms and Conditions or COling Services.<br/><br/><br/><b>Announcement date: 03/07, 2021<br/>Effective Date: 03/07, 2021</b>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="terms_personal" translatable="false">
        <![CDATA[
<br/>
    <p>"COling" (hereinafter referred to as "Company") shall comply with the relevant laws and regulations on privacy protection, such as the "Act on the Promotion of Information and Communication Network Use and Information Protection Act", "Telecommunication Secret Protection Act", and shall do its best to protect the user rights. The company shall use the user&apos;s personal information to the extent notified by [the purpose of collecting personal information], and shall not use the user&apos;s personal information beyond the same scope or provide or entrust the user&apos;s personal information to the outside without prior consent. However, exceptions are made in the case below.<br/><br/>If the user agrees in advance (if the user agrees in advance, means the user agrees to voluntarily provide his/her personal information to a third party for the use of the service, etc.) or if the investigation agency requests it according to the procedures and methods prescribed in the Act;<br/><br/>In such cases, the company notifies users (1) who receive personal information (2) their purpose of use (3) the retention and use period of personal information in advance and obtains explicit and individual consent. In all such processes, the company does not collect additional information against the user&apos;s will or share information beyond the scope of consent to third parties.</p><br/><br/><p><h3>Where to use personal information</h3><br/>COling collects user personal information for the purpose of utilization as follows:<br/><br/>1. Provide basic or specialized functions of the service<br/>2. If individual notice is required<br/>3. Resolution of inquiries or disputes regarding the use of the service<br/>4. Fulfillment of duties prescribed by Acts and subordinate statutes, etc.<br/>5. Prevention of misuse behavior that could harm you against laws and conditions of use.</p><br/><br/><br/><p><h3>The personal information we collect</h3><br/>
    1. email<br/>2. Pictures (including metadata)<br/>3. Device information (OS, screen size, device ID), IP address, cookie information<br/></p><br/><br/><p><h3>How to collect personal information</h3><br/>COling collects personal information in the following ways.<br/><br/><b>- Where a user agrees to collect personal information and enters information directly in the process of membership registration and service use<br/>- Where personal information is provided by affiliated services, organizations, etc.<br/>- Personal information collected from users in the course of service use<br/>- In the process of using the mobile app, information on device information (OS, screen size, device ID), IP address, cookies, and date of the visit can be automatically generated and collected.<br/>   </b>   </p>   <br/>   <br/>   <h3>Sharing and providing personal information</h3><br/>
COling does not use or provide or share user personal information to third parties beyond the scope of the purpose mentioned above, except when the user agrees to the service process, etc. or stipulated in the Act and subordinate statutes.<br/><br/><br/><h3>Period of personal information retention, method of destruction, and period of use;</h3><br/>All user personal information will be deleted and discarded when COling service membership is withdrawn.<br/><br/><br/><h3>Personal Information Contact</h3><br/>Please contact the person in charge of personal information protection for any inquiries, complaints, advice, or other matters concerning personal information protection caused by the user using the service.
 COling will do its best to listen to your voice and give you a quick and sufficient response.<br/><br/><br/><h3>Personal Information Protection Officer</h3><br/>Name: Hwajin Jung <br/> Email: comi01@gmail.com<br/><br/><br/><h3>A noticeable obligation</h3><br/>COling may modify the personal information processing policy for the purpose of reflecting changes in laws or services. If the personal information processing policy is changed, COling posts the changes, and the changed personal information processing policy takes effect seven days after the date of posting.<br/><br/><br/><b>Announcement date: 03/07, 2021<br/>Effective Date: 03/07, 2021</b>
        ]]>
    </string>


</resources>